Hi, in this final version, you will use Krosor to generate clean professional documentation
for your project.
Normally the kind of documentation is placed inside of Redmi.md file.
If you open this file, you will see.
But since that file is used already, as a guide for working with this repository and viewing
the source examples, you can click here on preview tab, and you can see the preview how
it looks on GitHub.
And you see this used as a guide how to use this repository with source code, how to download
it, etc.
So, and that's why we will create a separate documentation.md file instead.
But if you view generate for your personal project, I recommend you use Redmi.md file for
general documentation, and if you'd like to have some separate pages for the documentation
like describing how your feature works, how your apps inside works, etc.
You can create, of course, separate files to be the name of this apps.
OK.
So, the documentation will generate what it will include.
So, it will include a short overview of an application.
So, the name of the application and want to send a description what it does.
If you include its main feature, like swap the currencies, solentaring the amount, choosing
the Chrome and two currencies, loading data from API, etc.
It will also include the technical stack, this project used, the setup instructions, how
to run project, how to start this application, something like we have here.
It will also have a brief section with a use case, describing how to convert the currencies
in the applications.
So, and by the end of this lesson, you will have complete project documentation ready
for developers to read and reference.
OK.
Let's now generate it.
I will make my chat with the I bigger, and I already have a prompt.
You can find this prompt in materials to last some, in the beginning of this section.
Any ask AI generate developer documentation for this project and save it as documentation.md file
in this wrapper root.
I mean, a wrapper root is the main directory, so it will be stored right here.
I ask also include a short project overview and K features, technical stack, setup instructions,
how to install, run, build and test application, and also the usage guide with basic steps.
I will use agent mode to just allow it to create the documentation for me.
And let's run it.
So, we see to read all the files in the project to just have a more context, what's this
project about, we see generate in the documentation file, so when it will finish, I will also
open the preview.
So, we have the commutation.md, this is a markdown language, so we can read in this way.
But also, we can run the preview and see how it looks like, yeah, look more readable
format.
So, what it has, we have the project overview that it's a modern real-time currency converter
web application, which builds on React and TypeScript and et cetera, what it can does.
The key features, the test and the TypeScript loading states, a rock handling, input validation,
like emoji display, currency swapping, multi-currency support, real-time exchange rates, et cetera.
The technical stack, it describes what we use as a core technologist, what we use as testing
and what we use as API, and also the build tools we use.
There is also the type instructions, the private requirements, which not just version is
required to run this project, then also installations that we need to clone for the repository
of course, and install dependencies, and this will install the dependencies of course, the
development.
The development just run npm run dev, and open your website on this local host and this
port.
So, we specified the page automatic theory word for building for production, we run npm
run build, we can also run the preview, the production build, we can also run tests.
In watch mode, run tests once, run tests with UI, run coverage, I'm not sure this command
is actual, so anyway, you need to go through the generated documentation and just delete
what you don't need or by this time commands, you want to work because I'm not sure
npm run test UI, it's really something, we have it, yeah, okay, in UI it will try to
open this in browser it gets, okay, with any help the user you got, we have some basic
steps that you will first enter the mouse and select source currency target currency, get
exchange rate, and also can swap the currencies optional, and the application flow initial
flows, the application purchase of a currency, okay, a pay integration, what API we use, the
component structure, and there are handles, so we see a bit more information than we ask,
yeah, but I think it's useful, so we can click keep all and have in this documentation,
so this way you can easily generate documentation by AI for yourself, for the project, and
then you can make changes, so it's much easier because AI can provide a good structure,
it can describe it in a readable user friendly way, and you just need to change something
or delete if something is, you don't need, okay, I hope this was useful for you, and
see you in the next lessons.